<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Singularity Blogs</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Singularity Blogs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:05:32 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Anthonys Arch Setup</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/anthonys_arch_setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:05:32 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/anthonys_arch_setup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;anthonys-arch-setup&#34;&gt;Anthonys Arch Setup&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-boot-into-arch-and-run-the-installer&#34;&gt;1. Boot Into Arch and Run the Installer&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Create an Arch USB using Etcher or Ventoy.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Boot the laptop from USB.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;When the terminal loads, run:&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#282a36;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34; data-lang=&#34;bash&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;archinstall&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;install-settings&#34;&gt;Install Settings&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is what I did for these settings. Some are abvious and I&amp;rsquo;m not trying to be condisending. Think of this section as a checklist&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Archinstall language&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;Select_language = &amp;ldquo;English&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Locales&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;Keyboard_layout = &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Locale_language = &amp;rsquo;en_US.UTF-8&amp;quot;&#xA;Locale encoding = UTF-8&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making a Headless WordPress Next E commerce Site</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/making-a-headless-wordpress-next-ecommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/making-a-headless-wordpress-next-ecommerce/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;warning---this-blog-is-still-being-made-there-will-be-spelling-mistakes-bat-writing-and-it-will-end-ubrouptly&#34;&gt;Warning - This blog is still being made. There will be spelling mistakes, bat writing, and it will end ubrouptly.&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;why-do-this&#34;&gt;Why do this&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have found that my clients want lots of features on there site but don&amp;rsquo;t want to pay the price for them. Fine I say, I&amp;rsquo;ll set them up with wordpress and use the ocean of plugins to get them whatever they want without having to charge them the cost to make it myself. Clients also want to point at a pixel and say move a little to the left. Then they say, move it a little to to the right. Then they say a little to the left. They won&amp;rsquo;t direct the design of the entire site but little things here and there, they will want to influence. The issue is that with wordpress, you are using a template and the little changes on a template are very annoying to modify. You have to dig though an ocean of files and many times, those files are not very well organized. Additionaly, what looks good on a site is a combonation of three things, good UX (= good visuals), basic visual sciology, think the color wheele and complimenting colors, and whatever is trendy in the world of UI design. The last one, what is trendy sounds silly but I find it to be the difference between a $20 job and $200K job. Keeping up with the jonses is a silly idea but it really does affect the quality of how we see things. Here is the thing, the trendy UI designs are changing and will look very different every year and every 3 years, will look compleatly different.&#xA;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/img/mahwnecs/cdi_01.webp&#34; alt=&#34;Comparason&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;The templates on wordpress, as you can see look good, they have good UX and accessabality but they don&amp;rsquo;t look new and trendy. They belong in the year 2019. By time you read this, it may be much past the year 2026 but now, the images on the left look like much nicer looking websites. That is because on the left, it shows custom dribble designed pages. I have found dribble is a very up to date UI design site and I can tell the work there is new and trendy. Anyway, the point is wordpress templates are outdated looking and custom desings are cool and trendy looking. Now back to client work. If I where to propose a site to a client made fully custom, the price of that work would give the client sticker shock. Perhaps if I could just use wordpress but make my own template using a design frontend I am famalier with already. That is where the idea for this blog came from.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
