<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on Singularity Blogs</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on Singularity Blogs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Making a Headless WordPress Next E commerce Site</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/making-a-headless-wordpress-next-ecommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/making-a-headless-wordpress-next-ecommerce/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;why-do-this&#34;&gt;Why do this&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have found that my clients want lots of features on there site but don&amp;rsquo;t want to pay the price for them. Fine I say, I&amp;rsquo;ll set them up with wordpress and use the ocean of plugins to get them whatever they want without having to charge them the cost to make it myself. Clients also want to point at a pixel and say move a little to the left. Then they say, move it a little to to the right. Then they say a little to the left. They won&amp;rsquo;t direct the design of the entire site but little things here and there, they will want to influence. The issue is that with wordpress, you are using a template and the little changes on a template are very annoying to modify. You have to dig though an ocean of files and many times, those files are not very well organized. Additionaly, what looks good on a site is a combonation of three things, good UX (= good visuals), basic visual sciology, think the color wheele and complimenting colors, and whatever is trendy in the world of UI design. The last one, what is trendy sounds silly but I find it to be the difference between a $20 job and $200K job. Keeping up with the jonses is a silly idea but it really does affect the quality of how we see things. Here is the thing, the trendy UI designs are changing and will look very different every year and every 3 years, will look compleatly different.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
